<!-- Introduction to XML & XPath -->
<!-- A small snippet of the recipes.xml file for learning the basics! -->
<recipes>
	
	<recipe name="mineCandyTin" count="1">
		<ingredient name="resourceScrapIron" count="4" />
		<ingredient name="resourceGunPowder" count="4" />
		<ingredient name="resourceNail" count="1" />
		<ingredient name="resourceDuctTape" count="1" />
	</recipe>
	
	<recipe name="TunnelBoringMachine" count="1">
	
		<!-- see what we wrote on the FLIP Whiteboard at work -->
		<ingredient name="resourceDuctTape" count="200" />
		<ingredient name="resourceForgedIron" count="200" />
		<ingredient name="resourceMechanicalParts" count="200" />
		
	</recipe>
	
	<recipe name="drinkJarBoiledWater" count="1" craft_area="campfire" craft_tool="toolCookingPot">
		<ingredient name="drinkJarRiverWater" count="1" />
	</recipe>
	
	<recipe name="drinkJarGoldenRodTea" count="1" craft_area="campfire" craft_tool="toolCookingPot">
		<ingredient name="drinkJarBoiledWater" count="1" />
		<ingredient name="resourceCropGoldenrodPlant" count="1" />
	</recipe>
	
</recipes>

ELEMENTS AND ATTRIBUTES
What are the names of all the elements in the XML?
What are the names of some attributes in the XML?
What are the values of some attributes in the XML?
What is the name of the ROOT element of the XML document?
How many elements contain a craft_area attribute?
How many elements contain a count attribute with a value of 1?


BASIC XPATH (You'll need this for about 90% of what you do)

What XPath can we use to select the recipes element?	/recipes
What XPath can we use to select every recipe element inside the recipes one? /recipes/recipe
What XPath can we use to select only the recipe who has a name of drinkJarBoiledWater? /recipes/recipe[@name='drinkJarBoiledWater']
What XPath can we use to select every ingredient inside the mineCandyTin recipe? /recipes/recipe[@name='drinkJarBoiledWater']/ingredient 
What XPath can we use to select every ingredient that has a count attribute equal to 1? /recipes/recipe/ingredient[@count='1']
What XPath can we use to select every ingredient that has a count attribute NOT equal to 1? /recipes/recipe/ingredient[@count!='1']
What XPath can we use to select both the drinkJarBoiledWater and drinkJarGoldenRodTea recipes?
What XPath can we use to select only those recipes with a craft_tool attribute?
What XPath can we use to select the value of the drinkJarBoiledWater recipe's craft_tool attribute?
What XPath can we use to select the value of the craft_area attribute for the drinkJarGoldenRodTea recipe?
What XPath can we use to select only a recipe that does NOT have a craft_area attribute?

INDEX LOOKUP EXAMPLES (You may need this in certain situations)
What XPath can we use to select the first recipe WITHOUT using its name attribute value?
What XPath can we use to select the second recipe WITHOUT using its name attribute value?
What XPath can we use to select the third ingredient of the mineCandyTin recipe?
What XPath can we use to select the last recipe in the XML no matter how many recipes there are?
What XPath can we use to select the second-to-last recipe in the XML no matter how many recipes there are?